Archival Collective Bargaining Agreements File 6030
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Local 917 A-Z, 1970-1979 (Box 217, Folder 3)
- Local 648 A-Z, 1967-1970 (Box 217, Folder 4)
- Local 1015 A-Z, 1967-1970 (Box 217, Folder 5)
- Local 1030, 1969 (Box 217, Folder 6)
- Local 1034, 1970-1979 (Box 217, Folder 7)
- Local 1205 A-Z, 1967-1970 (Box 217, Folder 8)
- Local 364 E, 1966-1969 (Box 217, Folder 9)
- Local 364 A-B, 1960-1964 (Box 217, Folder 10)
- Local 364 C-D, 1969-1979 (Box 217, Folder 11)
- Local 364 M-R, 1968-1979 (Box 217, Folder 12)
- Local 364 S, 1970-1979 (Box 217, Folder 13)
- Local 364 T-Z, 1970-1979 (Box 217, Folder 14)
- Local 807, 1965-1967 (Box 218, Folder 1)
- Local 806, 1970-1979 (Box 218, Folder 2)
- Local 810 A-L, 1969-1979 (Box 218, Folder 3)
- Local 810 M-Z, 1969-1979 (Box 218, Folder 4)
- Local 854, 1969 (Box 218, Folder 5)
- Local 852 A-Z, 1967-1970 (Box 218, Folder 6)
- Local 802 A-Z, 1967-1970 (Box 218, Folder 7)
- Local 804 A-Z, 1969 (Box 218, Folder 8)
- Local 375 A-Z, 1967-1970 (Box 219, Folder 1)
- Local 317 Q-S, 1967-1970 (Box 219, Folder 2)
- Local 317 M-P, 1967-1970 (Box 219, Folder 3)
- Local 300 A-Z, 1967-1970 (Box 219, Folder 4)
- Local 317 T-Z, 1967-1970 (Box 219, Folder 5)
- Local 317 I-L, 1967-1970 (Box 219, Folder 6)
- Local 338 A-K, 1967-1970 (Box 219, Folder 7)
- Local 338 L-Z, 1969-1970 (Box 219, Folder 8)
- Local 364 F, 1966-1969 (Box 219, Folder 9)
- Local 364 G-H, 1968-1970 (Box 219, Folder 10)
- Local 316 A-Z, 1967-1970 (Box 219, Folder 11)
- Local 317 E-H, 1967-1970 (Box 219, Folder 12)
- Local 317 A-D, 1967-1970 (Box 219, Folder 13)
- Local 364 I-L, 1967-1970 (Box 219, Folder 14)
- Local 791 A-Z, 1967-1969 (Box 220, Folder 1)
- Local 719, 1966-1969 (Box 220, Folder 2)
- Local 669 Q-Z, 1966-1969 (Box 220, Folder 3)
- Local 645 A-Z, 1965-1969 (Box 220, Folder 4)
- Local 649 A-Z, 1966-1969 (Box 220, Folder 5)
- Local 787 A-Z, 1967-1969 (Box 220, Folder 6)
- Local 757 A-Z, 1967-1970 (Box 220, Folder 7)
- Local 39 A-Z, 1967-1970 (Box 220, Folder 8)
- Local 232 A-Z, 1966-1969 (Box 220, Folder 9)
- Local 237 A-Z, 1967-1970 (Box 220, Folder 10)
- Local 808, 1970 (Box 220, Folder 11)
- Local 46 A-Z, 1970 (Box 220, Folder 12)
- Local 182 A-Z, 1970 (Box 220, Folder 13)
- Local 138 A-Z, 1966-1969 (Box 220, Folder 14)
- Local 202 L-Z, 1966-1969 (Box 220, Folder 15)
- Local 202 A-K, 1966-1969 (Box 220, Folder 16)
- Local 3, 46, 1970 (Box 220, Folder 17)
- Local 118 A-Z, 1966-1969 (Box 221, Folder 1)
- Local 99 A-Z, 1965-1969 (Box 221, Folder 2)
- Local 111 A-Z, 1967-1970 (Box 221, Folder 3)
- Local 294 L-P, 1968-1970 (Box 221, Folder 4)
- Local 294 Q-S, 1967-1969 (Box 221, Folder 5)
- Local 294 T-Z, 1968 (Box 221, Folder 6)
- Local 295 A-Z, 1967-1970 (Box 221, Folder 7)
- Local 239 A-Z, 1967-1970 (Box 221, Folder 8)
- Local 282 A-Z, 1967-1970 (Box 221, Folder 9)
- Local 240 A-Z, 1969-1970 (Box 221, Folder 10)
- Local 263 A-Z, 1966-1969 (Box 221, Folder 11)
- Local 272 A-Z, 1966-1969 (Box 221, Folder 12)
- Local 294 A-D, 1967-1969 (Box 221, Folder 13)
- Local 62 (Box 221, Folder 14)
- Local 65 A-Z, 1965-1969 (Box 221, Folder 15)
- Local 80, 1967-1970 (Box 221, Folder 16)
- Local 27, 1967-1970 (Box 221, Folder 17)
- Teamsters 1919-1944 (Box 222, Folder 1)
- Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Halpers Int'l. Brotherhood of Agreements 1945-1949 (Box 222, Folder 2)
- Teamsters '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 222, Folder 3)
- Teamsters 1955-1959 (Box 222, Folder 4)
- Teamsters, Int'l. Brotherhood '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 222, Folder 5)
- Teamsters, 1967-1970 (Box 223, Folder 1)
- 1965-1970 (Box 223, Folder 2)
- 1971-1975 (Box 223, Folder 3)
- 1976-1980 (Box 223, Folder 4)
- 1981-1985 (Box 223, Folder 5)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America 223, 1961-1965 (Box 223, Folder 6)
- Technical Engineers, Int'l. Fed. Of Professional and (1977-) (Box 224, Folder 1)
- Technical Engineers Architects and Draftsmen, Int'l. Fed. Of, 1951 (Box 224, Folder 2)
- Telegraphers of America, Commercial Agreements 1945-1949 (Box 224, Folder 3)
- Telegraphers, Cont. '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 224, Folder 4)
- Telegraphers, 1955-1959 (Box 224, Folder 5)
- Telegraphers, Commercial 55-59, 1955-1959 (Box 224, Folder 6)
- Telegraph Workers, United, 1968-1973 (Box 224, Folder 7)
- Telegraphers Union, Commercial '60-'66, 1960-1966 (Box 224, Folder 8)
- Telephone Workers, Nat'l. Federation, 1955-1959 (Box 224, Folder 9)
- Teamsters, 1976 (Box 224, Folder 10)
- Telephone Employees, Michigan Federation of Agreements '44-'47, 1944-1947 (Box 225, Folder 1)
- Telephone Organizations, United Agreements '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 225, Folder 2)
- Telephone Union, Empire State Agreements '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 225, Folder 3)
- Telephone Workers, Empire State, 1950-1954 (Box 225, Folder 4)
- Telephone Workers, Empire State '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 225, Folder 5)
- Telephone Workers, Nat'l. Federation of Agreements '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 225, Folder 6)
- Telephone Workers, New England '50-'68, 1950-1968 (Box 225, Folder 7)
- Telephone Workers Union of New Jersey Agreements '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 225, Folder 8)
- Telephone Workers, N.J. '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 225, Folder 9)
- Telephone Workers, New York, 1954-1959 (Box 225, Folder 10)
- Telephone Workers, Organizing Committee Agreements '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 225, Folder 11)
- United Telephone Organizations '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 225, Folder 12)
- Telephone Org., United '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 225, Folder 13)
- Telephone Traffic Union (N.Y.), 1954-1959 (Box 225, Folder 14)
- Telephone Unions - Alliance 1950-1954 (Box 225, Folder 15)
- Telephone Unions- Alliance 1955-1959 (Box 225, Folder 16)
- Telephone Unions - Alliance 1960-1964 (Box 225, Folder 17)
- Telephone Unions - Alliance '65-'69, 1965-1969 (Box 225, Folder 19)
- Telephone Unions - Alliance 1970- (Box 225, Folder 20)
- Tennessee Vacancy Authority, AFL-CIO, 1940-1971 (Box 225, Folder 21)
- Textile Workers, United 1935-39, 1935-1939 (Box 226, Folder 1)
- 1920 Textile Workers (Box 226, Folder 2)
- Textile Workers, United AH '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 226, Folder 3)
- Textile Workers, United '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 226, Folder 4)
- Textile Workers - A.F.L. '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 226, Folder 5)
- Textile Workers, United '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 226, Folder 6)
- Textile Workers of America, United '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 226, Folder 7)
- Textile Workers, United 1965-69, 1965-1969 (Box 226, Folder 8)
- Textile Workers, United 1970-1975 (Box 226, Folder 9)
- Textile Workers Union of America - CIO Agreements, 1940-1943 (Box 226, Folder 10)
- Textile Workers Union '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 226, Folder 11)
- Textile Workers Union 1945-49 (cont.), 1945-1949 (Box 227, Folder 1)
- Textile Workers, 1952-1953 (Box 227, Folder 2)
- Textile Workers - CIO '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 227, Folder 3)
- Textile Workers of America - Agreements 1955-1959 (Box 228, Folder 1)
- Textile Workers, 1955-1959 (Box 228, Folder 2)
- Textile Workers, 1955-1959 (Box 228, Folder 3)
- Textile Workers, 1955-1959 (Box 228, Folder 4)
- Textile Workers, 1955-1959 (Box 228, Folder 5)
- Textile Workers, 1965-1970 (Box 229, Folder 1)
- Textile Workers, 1960-1964 (Box 229, Folder 2)
- Textile Workers, 1960-1965 (Box 229, Folder 3)
- Textile Workers Union (CIO) 1965-1969 (Box 229, Folder 4)
- Textile Workers Union (CIO) 1960-1964 (Box 229, Folder 5)
- TWUA - 1970 (Box 229, Folder 6)
- Tobacco Workers '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 230, Folder 1)
- Tobacco Workers '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 230, Folder 2)
- Tobacco Workers 1955-1959 (Box 230, Folder 3)
- Tobacco Workers 1960-1964 (Box 230, Folder 4)
- Tobacco Workers, 1965-1969 (Box 230, Folder 5)
- Tobacco Workers 1970-1974 (Box 230, Folder 6)
- Tobacco Workers '74-'77, 1974-1977 (Box 230, Folder 7)
- Toy and Novelty 1954-1959 (Box 230, Folder 8)
- Toy Workers, Doll and 1960 (Box 230, Folder 9)
- Train Dispatchers Union 1927- (Box 230, Folder 10)
- Transit Union; Amal., 1961 (Box 230, Folder 11)
- Transport Service, 1950-1954 (Box 230, Folder 12)
- Transport Service Employees, United 1956 (Box 230, Folder 13)
- Transport Workers Union of America Agreements 1945-1949 (Box 230, Folder 14)
- Transport Workers '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 230, Folder 15)
- Transport Workers '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 231, Folder 1)
- Transport Workers, 1954-1961 (Box 231, Folder 2)
- Transport Workers, 1960-1964 (Box 231, Folder 3)
- Transport Workers Union of America, 1960-1964 (Box 231, Folder 4)
- Transport Workers Union of America '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 231, Folder 5)
- Transport Workers, 1965-1969 (Box 231, Folder 6)
- Transport Workers 1965-1969 (Box 231, Folder 7)
- Transport 1970-75, 1970-1975 (Box 232, Folder 1)
- Transportation Union, United (UTU), 1968 (Box 232, Folder 2)
- UTU 1970- (Box 232, Folder 3)
- United Transportation Union, 1972 (Box 232, Folder 4)
- United Transportation Union, 1994 (Box 232, Folder 5)
- Transportation Union-Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers; United, 2001 (Box 232, Folder 6)
- Typographers 1907-1939 (Box 233, Folder 1)
- Typographical Union, International Agreement 1940-1944 (Box 233, Folder 2)
- Typographical Union, International Agreements 1945-1950 A-E (Box 233, Folder 3)
- Typographical Union, 1959-1964 (Box 233, Folder 4)
- Typographical '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 233, Folder 5)
- Typographical Union, Int'l. '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 233, Folder 6)
- Typographical Union '65-'69, 1965-1969 (Box 233, Folder 7)
- Typographical '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 233, Folder 8)
- Typographical Union 1970- (Box 233, Folder 9)
- University Employees Federation of 1970- (Box 233, Folder 10)
- United University Professions, 1995-2011 (Box 233, Folder 11)
- University Professors Amer. Assn., 1976-1978 (Box 233, Folder 12)
- Upholsterers Int'l. Union of N. America Agreements 1945-1949 (Box 234, Folder 1)
- Upholsterers' '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 234, Folder 2)
- Upholsterers' '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 234, Folder 3)
- Upholsterers 1965-1986 (Box 234, Folder 4)
- Utility Workers Organizing Committees Agreements '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 234, Folder 5)
- Utility Workers, 1954-1959 (Box 234, Folder 6)
- Utility Workers, America '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 234, Folder 7)
- Upholsterers' '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 234, Folder 8)
- Utility Workers '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 234, Folder 9)
- Utility Workers of America - Agreements '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 235, Folder 1)
- Utility Workers Union of America '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 235, Folder 2)
- Utility Workers Union 1965-1969 (Box 235, Folder 3)
- Utility Workers Union 1970-1979 (Box 235, Folder 4)
- Utility Workers Union 1970-79, 1970-1979 (Box 235, Folder 5)
- Utility Works Org. Comm. 1942-44, 1942-1944 (Box 235, Folder 6)
- Utility Workers of New England 1951 (Box 235, Folder 7)
- Wall Paper Craftmen '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 235, Folder 8)
- Wallpaper '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 236, Folder 1)
- Wallpaper '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 236, Folder 2)
- Watch workers Union, American 1944-1954 (Box 236, Folder 3)
- Watchmen's Assn. '50-'56, 1950-1956 (Box 236, Folder 4)
- Welders of America, 1953-1965 (Box 236, Folder 5)
- Woodworkers '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 236, Folder 6)
- Woodworkers of America International - Agreements 1945-1949 (Box 236, Folder 7)
- Woodworkers '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 236, Folder 8)
- Woodworkers; Int'l. 1955-1959 (Box 236, Folder 9)
- Writers Guild of America, 1960-1964 (Box 237, Folder 1)
- Writers Guild of America, 1963-1965 (Box 237, Folder 2)
- Writers Guild of America 1955-1959 (Box 237, Folder 3)
- Writers Guild of America 1988-92, 1988-1992 (Box 237, Folder 4)
- Writers Guild of America '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 237, Folder 5)
- A.C. Laurence Leather Worker's Union, 1949-1955 (Box 238, Folder 1)
- Air Carrier Mechanics Assoc., Int'l., 1954 (Box 238, Folder 2)
- Alleghany Mt. Gas Worker's Union, 1965-1967 (Box 238, Folder 3)
- Armco Employees Indep. Federation Inc., 1954-1960 (Box 238, Folder 4)
- Federation of American Workers, Nat'l., 1956 (Box 238, Folder 5)
- Arnold Bakers Employees Assoc., 1956 (Box 238, Folder 6)
- Atlantic Independent Union (Box 222), 1952-1956 (Box 238, Folder 7)
- Bakery Workers, United, 1959-1961 (Box 238, Folder 8)
- Auburn Shop Council (Box 238, Folder 9)
- Batavia Downs Employees' Ind. Unions, 1959 (Box 238, Folder 10)
- Beech-Nut Cooperative Council, 1955-1958 (Box 238, Folder 11)
- Beech-Nut Employee Assoc., 1955-1964 (Box 238, Folder 12)
- Beer Pump and Block Tin Plumbers, 1958 (Box 238, Folder 13)
- Biegel Bakers Union Bx 222 Agreements, 1964 (Box 238, Folder 14)
- Benzel Products Workmen's Organization (Box 238, Folder 15)
- Bloomingdale Dept. Store Employees Union - Distribute Workers Union, Ind., 1950-1956 (Box 238, Folder 16)
- Brewer Dry Dock Employees Assoc., Inc., 1960 (Box 238, Folder 17)
- Broadway Corp. Employees Council, 1960 (Box 238, Folder 18)
- Brooklyn Refining Independent Union, 1960-1963 (Box 238, Folder 19)
- Buffalo Yerkes Film Union, 1956 (Box 238, Folder 20)
- Bulk Distributing Plant Employee's Union, 1957 (Box 238, Folder 21)
- Bulk Distributing Plant Employee's Union, 1957 (Box 238, Folder 22)
- Business Machine and Office Appliance Mechanics Board, 1961 (Box 238, Folder 23)
- Butler Armco Employee Representatives (Box 222), 1950-1971 (Box 238, Folder 24)
- Candy Workers Union, United, 1950-1971 (Box 238, Folder 25)
- Candy Workers Union, United, 1952 (Box 238, Folder 26)
- Central Hudson Employees Assoc., 1965 (Box 238, Folder 27)
- Central State Petroleum Union Box 222 (Box 239, Folder 1)
- Chain Service Restaurant, Luncheonette and Soda Fountain Employees Union, 1960 (Box 239, Folder 2)
- Chapin Employees Assoc., 1959-1961 (Box 239, Folder 3)
- Chase, Brass and Copper Workers Union, 1950 (Box 239, Folder 4)
- Cherry - Burrell Independent Union, 1952-1961 (Box 239, Folder 5)
- Christian Labor Assoc., 1959-1961 (Box 239, Folder 6)
- Columbia Power Trade Council, 1945 (Box 239, Folder 7)
- Commercial Cable Staff's Assoc., 1951 (Box 239, Folder 8)
- Communication Equipment Workers Incorporated (Ind.), 1977 (Box 239, Folder 9)
- Connecticut Union of Telephone Workers, 1971-1978 (Box 239, Folder 10)
- Dairy Workers Association, United, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 11)
- Daystrom Industrial Independent Assoc., 1953-1957 (Box 239, Folder 12)
- Deepwater Officers Assoc., 1957-1959 (Box 239, Folder 13)
- Defender Employees Union, 1957-1960 (Box 239, Folder 14)
- Department Store Employees Union, 1949 (Box 239, Folder 15)
- Derrickmen and Riggers Assoc., United, 1967-1970 (Box 239, Folder 16)
- Die Casting Workers, 1938 (Box 239, Folder 17)
- Diesel Workers Union (Ind.), 1987-1990 (Box 239, Folder 18)
- East River Refinery Employees' Union of Socony- Mobil Oil Co., Inc., 1958 (Box 239, Folder 19)
- Electric Utility Employees' Union, 1954-1959 (Box 239, Folder 20)
- Electric and Machine Workers, Ind., 1948-1955 (Box 239, Folder 21)
- Electronics Union, Ind., 1960 (Box 239, Folder 22)
- Empire State Telephone Union, 1952-1953 (Box 239, Folder 23)
- Employees Assoc. Inc. of Colfate Palmotive, 1951-1957 (Box 239, Folder 24)
- Employees Assoc., Ind., of the Tobin Packing Co. - Albany Division, 1960-1965 (Box 239, Folder 25)
- Employees, Federation of, 1949-1954 (Box 239, Folder 26)
- Employees Mutual, Assoc., 1956 (Box 239, Folder 27)
- Employee Welfare Organization of the Hughes Tool Co., 1940-1941 (Box 239, Folder 28)
- Engineers Association, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 29)
- Engineers Assoc., 1954-1962 (Box 239, Folder 30)
- Engineers Assoc. of ARMA, 1953 (Box 239, Folder 31)
- Engineering Employees, Society of, 1961 (Box 239, Folder 32)
- Express Workers, American Fed. Of (Box 240, Folder 1)
- "Fabrikoid" Works Employees Assn., 1954 (Box 240, Folder 2)
- Federated Refrigeration and Automobile Workers Association, 1949-1956 (Box 240, Folder 3)
- Ferree Employees Ind. Union, 1960 (Box 240, Folder 4)
- Fiberglass and Plastic Industry, 1954-1958 (Box 240, Folder 5)
- File Workers Union, Ind., 1948 (Box 240, Folder 6)
- Filler Workers Group, 1960 (Box 240, Folder 7)
- Foundry and Metal Employees, 1957-1961 (Box 240, Folder 8)
- Futton County Plastics Workers, 1956-1961 (Box 240, Folder 9)
- Fused Cast Electrical Refractories Workers, Ind. Union of (Box 240, Folder 10)
- Geb and Souhan Employees' Assoc., 1958-1963 (Box 240, Folder 11)
- Consolidated Glove Culter's and Shavers' Union (Box 240, Folder 12)
- Glove Workers Union (Box 240, Folder 13)
- Guidance Counselors, Assoc. of, 1965-1967 (Box 240, Folder 14)
- Hand Covered Buckle and Nov. Assoc., 1961-1964 (Box 240, Folder 15)
- Hard Employees Union, 1957 (Box 240, Folder 16)
- Harper and Brothers Employees, Assoc. of, 1962 (Box 240, Folder 17)
- Harlem Labor Union (Box 240, Folder 18)
- Harper and Row Employees Assoc., 1957-1968 (Box 240, Folder 19)
- Houston Paper and Pulp Mill Workers, 1952-1954 (Box 240, Folder 20)
- Houston Works, 1958 (Box 240, Folder 21)
- Hub Oil Drivers and Maintenance Assoc., Inc., 1962 (Box 240, Folder 22)
- H.W. Wilson Company Employees Assoc., 1966-1968 (Box 240, Folder 23)
- Independent Pullman Wkrs. Federation (Box 223), 1937 (Box 240, Folder 24)
- Industrial Employees Assoc., Inc., 1950 (Box 240, Folder 25)
- Independent Workers of David Steel Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 240, Folder 26)
- Ivory doclet St. Bernard EE's Assoc., 1947 (Box 240, Folder 27)
- Jamestown Malleable Steelworkers Union, 1958 (Box 240, Folder 28)
- Laboratories Mechanics Union, Ind., 1957 (Box 240, Folder 29)
- Laboratories Protective Union, 1963 (Box 240, Folder 30)
- Librarians of the Detroit Public Library Assn. of Professional - Agreements, 1968 (Box 240, Folder 31)
- Library Employees, Federation of Agreements, 1969 (Box 240, Folder 32)
- L.C. Forman Employees Council, 1962 (Box 240, Folder 33)
- Licensed Tugmen's and Pilot's (AFL-CIO) Protective Assoc. of America, 1959 (Box 240, Folder 34)
- Loyal Workers Group, 1958-1962 (Box 240, Folder 35)
- Machine Printers and Engravers Assoc. of the U.S., 1962 (Box 240, Folder 36)
- Machinery Erection Workers of America, 1945 (Box 240, Folder 37)
- Macy Department Store Employees' Union, 1951 (Box 240, Folder 38)
- Maintenance and Service Employees' Union, 1948 (Box 240, Folder 39)
- Mallinckrodt Chemical Labor Union, 1963-1969 (Box 240, Folder 40)
- Manhattan Street Employees' Union, 1958-1965 (Box 240, Folder 41)
- Marine Technicians Guild, 1961 (Box 240, Folder 42)
- Maryland Federation of Telephone Workers, 1947-1948 (Box 240, Folder 43)
- Maryland Telephone Union, Inc. Box 223, 1970 (Box 240, Folder 44)
- Mechanical and Electrical Workers Union of America, 1949 (Box 240, Folder 45)
- Merchants Ladies Garm., 1943-1948 (Box 240, Folder 46)
- Metal Engravers Union (Box 240, Folder 47)
- Meter Workers Union, 1957-1959 (Box 240, Folder 48)
- Metropolitan Funeral Directors Assoc., Inc., 1962 (Box 240, Folder 49)
- Metropolitan Protective Union (Box 240, Folder 50)
- Michigan Telephone Employee's Federation, Inc., 1946 (Box 240, Folder 51)
- Milk Driver and Dairy Employees (N.Y.C. Local), 1964 (Box 240, Folder 52)
- Minneapolis Federation of Honeywell Engineers, 1956 (Box 240, Folder 53)
- Mobile Terminal EE's Association (Box 240, Folder 54)
- Narrow Fabric Workers Union of Vogt Mfg., 1963 (Box 240, Folder 55)
- New England Petroleum Labor Organizing Operating Unit (Box 240, Folder 56)
- New York State Pipeline Contractors Assoc., 1964 (Box 240, Folder 57)
- New York State Pipeline Union (Box 240, Folder 58)
- Niagara Hooker Employees Union, 1955-1962 (Box 240, Folder 59)
- Niagara Plan and Employees Union, 1957-1975 (Box 240, Folder 60)
- Non-Technical Employees Assoc., 1957 (Box 240, Folder 61)
- Northern Oil Workers Unions, 1959 (Box 240, Folder 62)
- Independent Oil and Chemical Workers Union, 1960 (Box 240, Folder 63)
- Oil Refinery EE's Assn., 1945 (Box 240, Folder 64)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers, 1968 (Box 240, Folder 65)
- Oxford Employees Ind. Union, 1958-1964 (Box 240, Folder 66)
- Pacific Gen Worker Union, 1942 (Box 241, Folder 1)
- Palmyra Independent Workers, 1959 (Box 241, Folder 2)
- Paper Box Workers, Ind. (Box 241, Folder 3)
- Papermill Workers, 1945 (Box 241, Folder 4)
- Parking garage Employees' Assoc., 1958 (Box 241, Folder 5)
- P.C.K. Employees' Union, Ind., 1957 (Box 241, Folder 6)
- Penn. N.Y. Pipe Line System, Assoc. of, 1952 (Box 241, Folder 7)
- Pennsylvania Telephone Guild, 1980 (Box 241, Folder 8)
- Petroleum Assoc. of Labor, 1959-1964 (Box 241, Folder 9)
- Petroleum Union of Buffalo Refinery Employees', 1954 (Box 241, Folder 10)
- Petroleum Workers, Ind. '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 241, Folder 11)
- Petroleum Workers, Independent Union of Agreements, 1952-1958 (Box 241, Folder 12)
- Petroleum Workers (Ind) 1950-1960 (Box 241, Folder 13)
- Petroleum Workers, Independent Union of (1965-1969) (Box 241, Folder 14)
- Phillips Foundry Non-Affiliated Shop Union, 1962 (Box 241, Folder 15)
- Piano Workers, Ind. Union of, 1959-1962 (Box 241, Folder 16)
- Plant Protection Employees, Ind., 1960 (Box 241, Folder 17)
- Plumbers Co. Workers Amer. (Box 241, Folder 18)
- Point Breeze Hourly Employees' Association (Bx 224), 1950-1954 (Box 241, Folder 19)
- Power City Union, Ind., 1957 (Box 241, Folder 20)
- Power Tools Employee's Ind., 1967 (Box 241, Folder 21)
- Processing, Maintenance and Distributing Workers of America, Assoc. of, 1964 (Box 241, Folder 22)
- Procter and Gamble Independent Union of Port Ivory, N.Y., 1951-1959 (Box 241, Folder 23)
- Production Employees Group of the Bulova Watch Co., 1964 (Box 241, Folder 24)
- Production Service and Sales Employees Union, Int'l., 1959-1962 (Box 241, Folder 25)
- Professional Personnel, Assoc. of, 1958 (Box 241, Folder 26)
- Progressive Sugar Refinery Workers, of America, 1967 (Box 241, Folder 27)
- Pullman - Sand A/C Union, 1945 (Box 241, Folder 28)
- Pullman Co., 1937-1944 (Box 241, Folder 29)
- Pulverizing and Processing Union, United, 1952-1956 (Box 241, Folder 30)
- Radio Writers Guild, 1954 (Box 241, Folder 31)
- Order of railway Conductors, 1952-1954 (Box 241, Folder 32)
- Railway Expressmen, Order of, 1924-1927 (Box 241, Folder 33)
- Rets of Employees, Assoc. of International Salt Co., 1956-1958 (Box 241, Folder 34)
- Rochester Independent Union, 1954 (Box 241, Folder 35)
- Rochester Printing Craft Union, 1957-1959 (Box 241, Folder 36)
- Sailors Union, Lake, 1955-1957 (Box 241, Folder 37)
- Salaried Union, Ind. 1950-1966 (Box 241, Folder 38)
- Salary Policy Employee Panel, 1950-1952 (Box 241, Folder 39)
- Savage Employees Protective Organization, 1956 (Box 241, Folder 40)
- Schenectady Draftsmen, Assoc., 1955-1960 (Box 241, Folder 41)
- Screen Directors Guild of America, 1958 (Box 241, Folder 42)
- Screen Directors' Int'l. Guild, 1964 (Box 241, Folder 43)
- Seneca Falls Machine Employees Assoc., 1957 (Box 241, Folder 44)
- Social Agency Employees, United, 1949-1951 (Box 242, Folder 1)
- Social Service Employees' Union, 1962 (Box 242, Folder 2)
- Society of Airline Meteorologists, 1949 (Box 242, Folder 3)
- Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers, 1964 (Box 242, Folder 4)
- Socony - Mobil (Ind.) Boatmen's Union, 1956 (Box 242, Folder 5)
- Socony Paint Products - Employees Union, 1949 (Box 242, Folder 6)
- Socony Vacuum Tanker Men's Assoc., 1960 (Box 242, Folder 7)
- Southern Calif. Master Labor Agreements Bx. 225 (Box 242, Folder 8)
- So Cal. Professional Engineering Association, 1949 (Box 242, Folder 9)
- Standard and Poor's Ind. Assoc., 1959-1960 (Box 242, Folder 10)
- Standard Oil EE's Ass'n., 1945 (Box 242, Folder 11)
- Steel Workers Union, Ind., 1956 (Box 242, Folder 12)
- Sugar Workers Union, Ind., 1959-1961 (Box 242, Folder 13)
- Supervisors of Kosher Food Service, 1965 (Box 242, Folder 14)
- Syracuse Employee's Council Assoc., 1958 (Box 242, Folder 15)
- Tech Tape Employees Ind., Assoc., 1963 (Box 242, Folder 16)
- Telephone Clerks of Illinois, Federation of, 1952-1955 (Box 242, Folder 17)
- Telephone Commercial Union, 1966-1971 (Box 242, Folder 18)
- Telephone Commercial Union, Diamond State, 1971 (Box 242, Folder 19)